A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Latin America and the Caribbean, Correspondence Files of Thomas J. Trebat FA611
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Latin America and the Caribbean, Correspondence Files of Thomas J. Trebat
1989-1992
Rockefeller Archive Center
Trebat, Thomas J.
Ford Foundation
FA611
1.31 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Arrangement
Chronological
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
Contains correspondence.
Biographical / Historical
Thomas Trebat is a professor, economist, and former foundation executive. From 1989 to 1992, he was Regional Director for the Ford Foundation's Latin America and Caribbean Program.
Trebat's post-Ford Foundation career included positions as head of Emergency Market Research at Citicorp Securities and Managing Director and Head of the Latin America team in the Economic and Market Analysis department of Citigroup. In 2005, he joined Columbia University. He earned a Ph.D. in economics from Vanderbilt University.
- Chronological Correspondence, 1989-1992; I (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1989 August-October (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1989 November (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1989 December (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 January (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 February (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 March (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 April (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 May (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 June (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 July (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 August (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 September (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 October (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 November (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1990 December (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 January (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 February (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 March (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 April (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 May (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 June (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 July (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 August (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 September (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 October (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 November (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1991 December (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 January (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 February (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 March (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 April (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 May (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 June (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 July (Box 1)
  - Chrons, 1992 August-October 1 (Box 1)